Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Subject Files, 1933-2010; 447315
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - The Press, cuid16632; 447806 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Protests, cuid16633; 447807 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Protests, 1991-1992, undated; cuid16634; 447808 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Gulf Wars: 1990-1991, First Gulf War - Zinn Articles, Drafts, Notes, 1991, undated; cuid16635; 447809 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis, 1990-1994, 1997-1998, undated; cuid16636; 447821 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis, 1998-2000, undated; cuid16637; 447822 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Gulf Wars: 1998, Iraq Crisis - Correspondence between Zinn and Barney Frank, cuid16638; 447823 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, 2001-2008, undated; cuid16639; 447824 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, Casualties, Oct 2001-Nov 2001; cuid16640; 447825 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Afghanistan, Casualties, Dec 2001-2003, undated; cuid16641; 447827 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Anti-war Resistance / Actions, 2002-2003; cuid16642; 447828 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Anti-war Resistance / Actions, 2004-2005; cuid16643; 447829 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Bombing, Casualties, 2003, undated; cuid16644; 447830 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Hypocrisy, 2003-2004, undated; cuid16645; 447831 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, 2002-2008, undated; cuid16646; 447832 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, Anti-War Opinion, 2003-2004; cuid16647; 447833 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, Casualties, 2003-2006, undated; cuid16648; 447834 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Iraq, U.S. Handover, 2004-2005, undated; cuid16649; 447835 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Lies, 2002-2003, undated; cuid16650; 447836 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Occupation, 2002-2003; cuid16651; 447837 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Occupation, 2004-2005, undated; cuid16652; 447838 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - Torture, 2004-2005, undated; cuid16653; 447839 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Gulf Wars: 2001-, Afghanistan and Iraq - U.S.-Iraq History, 1999, 2002-2008, undated; cuid16654; 447840 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Gulf Wars: Guantanamo, 2004-2009, undated; cuid16655; 447841 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Gulf Wars: Iraq, 1990-2000, undated; cuid16656; 447842 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Gulf Wars: "A Threat to Peace" (poster), [2002]; cuid16657; 448800 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Haiti, undated; cuid16658; 447843 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii, undated; cuid16659; 447844 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Health Issues, 1968-2007, undated; cuid16660; 447845 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Health Issues: "Consumer Interest and Health Reform: The Logic of Withdrawal from Managed Competition" Presentation by Gordon D. Schiff, M.D., 1994; cuid16661; 447846 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Helms, Richard: Perjury Case, 1977; cuid16662; 447847 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings, 1996; cuid16663; 447848 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings, 1998; cuid16664; 447849 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Chained and Unchained", 2006-2007; cuid16665; 447850 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Kevin, Monkey Monk and the Atomic Funk", 2006; cuid16666; 447851 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "The Phoenix", 1996; cuid16667; 447852 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - Rebel Angel or The Confessions of an Angry Nigger!, 1992; cuid16668; 447853 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Hicks, Kevin: Writings - "Valley of the Shadows or Diary of Darkness", 1993; cuid16669; 447854 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - History, 1954, 1965-1981; cuid16670; 447855 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - History, 1969-1994; cuid16671; 447856 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - History, 1985-1997; cuid16672; 447857 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - History, 1995-2006, undated; cuid16673; 447858 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - History, 1998-2003; cuid16674; 447859 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - History, 2003-2007; cuid16675; 447860 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - History (I), undated; cuid16676; 447861 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - History (II), undated; cuid16677; 447920 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - History: Alien and Sedition Act (1798), 1967, undated; cuid16678; 447921 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - History: American Revolution, 1979, 1992, 2004, undated; cuid16679; 447922 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - History: Archives, "Oral History of the American Left" (newsletter), 1979-1980, undated; cuid16680; 447928 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - History: Class Conflict - 19th Century, 1979, 1988, undated; cuid16681; 447929 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - History: Essays (by Zinn and others), 1975-1982, undated; cuid16682; 447930 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - History: Haymarket Riots, 1986, undated; cuid16683; 447931 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - History: Manifest Destiny, 1941-2004, undated; cuid16684; 447932 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - History: Mexican War, 1979; cuid16685; 447933 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - History: The New Deal, 1967-1993, undated; cuid16686; 447934 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - History: Notes, 1967-1973, undated; cuid16687; 447935 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - History: Philosophy of History, 1988, undated; cuid16688; 447936 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - History: Potency, 1975-1979, undated; cuid16689; 447937 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - History: Science and History, 1967-1982, undated; cuid16690; 447938 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - History: The Sixties, 1979, 1997, 1999, undated; cuid16691; 447939 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - History: The Sixties, undated; cuid16692; 447940 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - History: Socialist Movements of the Early 20th Century, 1968, 1979-1989, undated; cuid16693; 447941 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - History: Truman Administration, 1955-1956, 1964, 1974, undated; cuid16694; 447942 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - History: U.S. Bibliography, 1970-1978; cuid16695; 447944 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - History: U.S. Bibliography, 1975-1978, undated; cuid16696; 447945 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - History: U.S. Diplomatic History, 1959, undated; cuid16697; 447946 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - History: U.S. History (class), 1956-2001, undated; cuid16698; 447947 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - History: U.S. and Latin America, 1979-1986, 2003, undated; cuid16699; 447948 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - History: Wilson, Woodrow - Foreign Policy Pre-WWI, undated; cuid16700; 447949 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - History: Works Progress Administration (WPA), 1937, 1978, 1995, undated; cuid16701; 447950 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - History: World History, undated; cuid16702; 447951 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - History: World War I, 1939, 1972, undated; cuid16703; 447953 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - History: World War II, 1945-1955, undated; cuid16704; 447954 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - History and Science: Objectivity, 1965-1992, undated; cuid16705; 447955 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - The Holocaust, 1979-1989, 2003, undated; cuid16706; 447958 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - The Holocaust: Notes on Peter Novick's The Holocaust in American Life (1999), undated; cuid16707; 447959 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Hope, 1990s; cuid16708; 447960 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Hope, 2000; cuid16709; 447961 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Hope, 2001; cuid16710; 447962 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Hope (includes letter from Patch Adams), Jan 2002-Jul 2002; cuid16711; 447963 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Hope, Sep 2002-Dec 2002; cuid16712; 447964 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Hope, 2003; cuid16713; 447965 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Hope, 2004; cuid16714; 447966 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Hope, 2005; cuid16715; 447967 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Hope, 2006-2009, undated; cuid16716; 447968 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Hope: "The People Speak" Script, Notes, 2009; cuid16717; 447969 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1968-1974, undated; cuid16718; 447970 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1971-1973, undated; cuid16719; 447971 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues, 1975-1976; cuid16720; 447972 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Housing and Tenant Issues: "The Gordon Empire: A Tenant Research Report", 1975; cuid16721; 447973 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Human Nature, 1964-1988; cuid16722; 447974 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Human Nature, undated; cuid16723; 447975 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Human Nature: Why War? by Albert Einstein and Sigmund Freud (pamphlet), 1933; cuid16724; 447976 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Human Rights, 1987-1994, undated; cuid16725; 447977 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Human Rights: USSR, 1965-1980, undated; cuid16726; 447978 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Human Rights: Various Eastern European Countries - Czechoslovakia, Poland, Yugoslavia, East Germany, 1964-1974, undated; cuid16727; 447979 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Ideology, undated; cuid16728; 447980 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Ideology: Education, 1969-1988, undated; cuid16729; 447981 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Ideology: Education - Bloom, Allan, 1986-1991, undated; cuid16730; 447982 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Ideology: Political Theory, 1959-1987, undated; cuid16731; 447989 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ideology: Political Theory (includes course outline and notes), 1976-1989, undated; cuid16732; 447990 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Ideology: The University, 1966-1984, undated; cuid16733; 447991 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Imperialism, 1965-1981, undated; cuid16734; 447992 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Imperialism: "The American Empire and the U.S. Economy" Reprint from The Age of Imperialism by Harry Magdoff, 1973; cuid16735; 447993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Imperialism: Economics of Imperialism, 1975-1981, undated; cuid16736; 447994 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Imperialism: Exceptionalism, 2008, undated; cuid16737; 447995 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Imperialism: Imperial Expansion, 2003; cuid16738; 447996 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Imperialism: Imperialism Materials, 1962-1977, undated; cuid16739; 447997 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Imperialism: Imperialism Materials (various articles and essays selected and annotated by Zinn), 1950s, 1960s, 1970s; cuid16740; 447998 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Imperialism: Post-World War II, 1975-1979, undated; cuid16741; 447999 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Imperialism: Third World (includes lengthy letter from Peace Corps volunteer re: situation in Mali and Ivory Coast), 1974-1980, undated; cuid16742; 448000 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - India, 1947-2006, undated; cuid16743; 448001 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Indians: The Conquest of America, How the Indian Nations Lost Their Continent by Hans Koning, 1993; cuid16744; 448007 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Indians: History, 1989-2009, undated; cuid16745; 448002 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Indians: History, Early, 1997, 2000-2005, undated; cuid16746; 448003 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Indians: History, Early (research materials - notes, articles), 1976-1978, undated; cuid16747; 448004 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Indians: History - Post-Civil War (research materials - notes, articles), 1953, 1977, undated; cuid16748; 448005 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Indians: History - Removal (research materials - notes, articles), 1969, 1975, undated; cuid16749; 448006 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Indians: Recent Years, 1954-1976; cuid16750; 448008 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Indians: Recent Years, 1977-1978, undated; cuid16751; 448009 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Insurgency (Latin America), 1967, 1968, undated; cuid16752; 448010 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - International: Items of Interest, 2001-2005; cuid16753; 448011 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - International: Items of Interest, 2002-2005, undated; cuid16754; 448012 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Irons, Peter, 1971, 1980; cuid16755; 448013 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - "Just War" (includes E. Haldeman-Julius Little Blue Book 1547 sent to Zinn by Kurt Vonnegut), 1991, 2008, undated; cuid16756; 448014 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Kerry, John, 2004; cuid16757; 448015 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1972- Oct 1974; cuid16758; 448016 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Kissinger, Henry, Nov 1974-2002, undated; cuid16759; 448017 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Kosovo, 1998-2000, undated; cuid16760; 448018 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Kropotkin, Peter, 1969, undated; cuid16761; 448019 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Labor: Boston's Labor Movement, An Oral History of Work and Union Organizing (The Boston 200 Corporation), 1977; cuid16762; 448020 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Labor: "Corporate Strategies and Workers' Lives: The Dow Strike, 1974" by Brady Mikusko, 1978; cuid16763; 448021 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Labor: History - General, 1978-1997, undated; cuid16764; 448022 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Labor: History - Lawrence Strike, 1955-1973, undated; cuid16765; 448023 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Labor: Law, 1975-1981; cuid16766; 448024 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Labor: Law, 1982-1985; cuid16767; 448025 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Labor: Law (I), undated; cuid16768; 448026 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Labor: Law (II), undated; cuid16769; 448027 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Labor: Law - Lecture, 1983-1984, undated; cuid16770; 448028 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Labor: Tactics, 1969-1976, undated; cuid16771; 448029 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Labor: Work (includes a student paper, "A Working Class Hero: From a Daughter's Perspective"), 1974-1987, undated; cuid16772; 448031 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Labor: Workers, 1973-1976, undated; cuid16773; 448032 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Labor: Yale University Strike, 1984; cuid16774; 448033 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Lafferty, James, et al. v. William Rogers, et al. (Zinn one of the plaintiffs), 1971-1973; cuid16775; 448036 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Law: Class and Law, 1969-1989, 2005-2006, undated; cuid16776; 448040 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Law: Constitutional Theory and the Supreme Court, 1985-1988, undated; cuid16777; 448041 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Law: Constitutional Theory and the Supreme Court - Bork, Roberts (nominee); Justices Scalia, Kennedy and Alito, 1986-2006; cuid16778; 448042 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Law: Constitutional Theory and the Supreme Court - Chief Justice William Rehnquist, 1982-1987; cuid16779; 448043 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Law: General, 1971-1999, undated; cuid16780; 448044 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Law: "Ideology in the Courtroom" by Howard Zinn and Laura Stewart (New England Law Review), 1985-1986; cuid16781; 448046 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Law: International Law, 2003, undated; cuid16782; 448048 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Law: Jury Nullification, 1970, 1985, 2004; cuid16783; 448049 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Law: Justice 1986, 1975-1986, undated; cuid16784; 448050 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Law: Law and Justice, 2003-2008, undated; cuid16785; 448051 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Law: Law and War, 1961-1985, undated; cuid16786; 448052 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Law: The Rule of Law (annotated articles and notes), 1959, 1960, undated; cuid16787; 448053 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Law: Sexual Justice and Law, 1980, undated; cuid16788; 448054 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Law: Supreme Court Cases, 1992-1995, 2009, undated; cuid16789; 448055 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Law: Wealth and Law, 1967-1985, undated; cuid16790; 448056 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Law: Wealth and Law, 1970-1986, undated; cuid16791; 448057 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - ["Le Movement Neoconservateur aux Etats-Unis"] (incomplete French-language manuscript re: Neoconservatism in the US), undated; cuid16792; 448058 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Libya: U.S. Deception, 1986, 1987; cuid16793; 448059 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - LSD and Dirty Tricks, 1975, undated; cuid16794; 448060 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - MacDonald, Alex: Howard Zinn Lecture Series, 2006-2009; cuid16795; 448061 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Machiavelli, 1963, 1964, 1971, 1988, undated; cuid16796; 448062 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Mark, Karl: General, 1975-2000, undated; cuid16797; 448063 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Marx, Karl: Hegel, 1975, undated; cuid16798; 448064 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Marx, Karl: Views on History and Structure, 1984, undated; cuid16799; 448065 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Marx, Karl: Zinn Notes on Writings - The 18th Brumaire of Louis Bonaparte, undated; cuid16800; 448066 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Marx, Karl: Zinn Notes on Writings - The German Ideology, undated; cuid16801; 448067 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Marx, Karl: Zinn Notes on Writings - Manuscripts of 1844 - Alienation, 1958-1959, undated; cuid16802; 448068 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Marxism: Articles, Bibliographies and Class Syllabi, 1959-2000, undated; cuid16803; 448069 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Marxism: Economics, 1975-1984, undated; cuid16804; 448070 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Marxism: Existentialism, 1962-1975, undated; cuid16805; 448071 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Marxism: General, 1961-1962, undated; cuid16806; 448072 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Marxism: The State, 1960-1987, undated; cuid16807; 448073 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Marxism: U.S.Culture, 1967, undated; cuid16808; 448074 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Massacres, 1976, 1999, undated; cuid16809; 448075 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Media, 1989-2005, undated; cuid16810; 448076 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Middle East: Israel - Arms Trade and U.S. Aid, 1980-1987, undated; cuid16811; 448077 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Middle East: Israel - Occupied Territories, West Bank and Gaza, 1979-2009, undated; cuid16812; 448078 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Middle East: Israel and Lebanon - 1982 Invasion and Aftermath, 1981-1997, undated; cuid16813; 448079 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Middle East: Israel and Palestine Conflict, 1946, 1948, 1982, 1998-2003, undated; cuid16814; 448080 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Middle East: Israel and Palestine Conflict, 1974-1991, undated; cuid16815; 448081 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Middle East: Israel and Palestine Conflict - Western Perceptions, 1973, 1982; cuid16816; 448082 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Moral Development, undated; cuid16817; 448083 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - More, Thomas, 1949, 1985, undated; cuid16818; 448084 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Multi-Culturalism, 1991-1998, undated; cuid16819; 448085 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - The New Left, 1959, 1965, 1967; cuid16820; 448086 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - The New Left, 1968-1969, undated; cuid16821; 448087 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - The New Left: "The New Left, Memorandum Prepared for the Subcommittee to Investigate the Administration of the Internal Security Act and other Internal Security Laws...", 1968; cuid16822; 448088 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - The New Left: Notes, undated; cuid16823; 448089 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - New Progressive Parties, 1993, 1994, undated; cuid16824; 448090 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - New World Order, 1991-1998; cuid16825; 448091 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - New World Order, 1999-2002, undated; cuid16826; 448092 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1994, 2001, undated; cuid16827; 448093 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Administration - General, 1973-1975, 1981, undated; cuid16828; 448094 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Corporations, 1966, 1973-1974, undated; cuid16829; 448095 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Ford (Gerald R.), After Watergate, 1973-1975, undated; cuid16830; 448096 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Resignation and Post-Watergate, 1974-1975, undated; cuid16831; 448097 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), Apr 1973-May 1973; cuid16832; 448098 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), Jun 1973-Jul 1973; cuid16833; 448099 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), Aug 1973-Dec 1973; cuid16834; 448100 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings), 1974; cuid16835; 448101 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate (clippings and notes), 1975, 1992, undated; cuid16836; 448102 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - and the Legal System, 1973-1984, undated; cuid16837; 448103 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - Overview, 1973-1976, undated; cuid16838; 448104 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - Special Treatment, 1975, 1978, undated; cuid16839; 448105 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Nixon, Richard M.: Watergate - Surveillance, 1970, 1973-1975; cuid16840; 448106 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Obama, Barack, 2009-2010, undated; cuid16841; 448107 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert Case (clippings), 1954; cuid16842; 448108 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - "An Oral History": Graduate Thesis, Boston University School of Journalism, by Stephen Coleman, 1976; cuid16843; 448109 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Organizations: Various (publicity, solicitations and related materials), 1971-2000, undated; cuid16844; 448110 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Paris Commune, undated; cuid16845; 448111 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Paris Commune: The 31 Official Sessions of the Paris Commune (I), undated; cuid16846; 448112 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Paris Commune: The 31 Official Sessions of the Paris Commune (II), undated; cuid16847; 448113 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Paris Commune: Les 31 Seances Officielles de la Commune De Paris (1871), undated; cuid16848; 448114 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Paris: May 1968 - Aftermath, 1968, undated; cuid16849; 448115 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Paris: University of Vincennes - Relocation, 1977-1978, undated; cuid16850; 448116 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Party Tactics: Revisionism and Eurocommunism, 1987, undated; cuid16851; 448117 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Patriotism / Nationalism, 1980-1991, undated; cuid16852; 448118 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Peekskill Concert (Paul Robeson), 1949, 1976; cuid16853; 448119 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - The Philippines, 1970, undated; cuid16854; 448120 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Plato, the Greeks, 1981-1988, undated; cuid16855; 448121 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Poetry, 1992, 2002-2005, undated; cuid16856; 448122 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Police, 1963-1969; cuid16857; 448123 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Police, 1970-1979; cuid16858; 448124 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Police, 1980-1987; cuid16859; 448125 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Police, 1990-2006, undated; cuid16860; 448126 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Police: Community Control of Police (includes Washington D.C. proposal), 1968, undated; cuid16861; 448127 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Police: Publications - Day of Protest, Night of Violence, the Century City Peace March, 1967; cuid16862; 448128 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Police: Publications - Law and Disorder, the Chicago Convention and its Aftermath, [1968]; cuid16863; 448129 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Police: Publications - The Nation, Special Issue - "The Cops", 1969; cuid16864; 448130 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Police: Publications - The Nation, Special Issue - "Law and Order", 1970; cuid16865; 448131 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Police: Student Papers, 1970-1971, undated; cuid16866; 448132 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Politics: National Politics, 1967-1974, undated; cuid16867; 448133 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Politics: The Political System, 2008; cuid16868; 448134 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Politics: Psychology and Politics, 1955-1980, undated; cuid16869; 448135 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - The Politics of Nonviolent Action by Gene Sharp: Reviews, 1973-1974; cuid16870; 448136 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Popper, Karl, 1982, undated; cuid16871; 448137 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Posters: Alternative Alphabet, 1998; cuid16872; 448802 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Posters: Boycott Grapes, undated; cuid16873; 448803 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Posters: "Esperanza Chiapas", undated; cuid16874; 448804 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - Posters: Russian Language Poster, undated; cuid16875; 448806 (Flat-file-folder 7)
  - The Post-Revolutionary State, 1980-1987, undated; cuid16876; 448138 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - The Post-Revolutionary State (clippings), 1968-1990, undated; cuid16877; 448139 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Poverty, 1998. 2001-2003, undated; cuid16878; 448140 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - "President Clinton, A Corporate Offensive and Okinawa Bases" by Daniel B. Schirmer, 2000; cuid16879; 448141 (Box 61, Folder 20)